tombraiders.net 2019-04-27

# Privacy Policy for Tombraiders.net | Stella's Site

This page was last updated on 5/20/18.

##### GENERAL

Tombraiders.net respects your right to privacy. The following outlines the privacy policy for this site, as well as for its sister sites, [BrickRaiders.net](http://brickraiders.net/) and [SpaceColonyFans.net](http://www.spacecolonyfans.net/). I have made every attempt to keep all three sites fully GDPR-compliant. If you have any questions, please feel free to email ([stellalune@tombraiders.net](mailto:stellalune@tombraiders.net)) or contact me through my [web form](https://tombraiders.net/stella/contact.html).

##### PERSONAL EMAIL & OPT-IN BLOG NOTIFICATIONS

There are no password-restricted areas on my sites and, unless you contact me, I have no way of obtaining your email address or other personal information.

When you send me a message by email or through my [contact form](https://tombraiders.net/stella/contact.html), I do receive your name or nickname (if you have provided it), email address, and IP address (Internet Protocol). I  _never_ , under any circumstances, rent, sell or share this information with any outside parties. Sending me a personal message will not cause you to receive any "spam"/junk email.

The only exceptions to this rule are contests and charity drives. For contests/raffles, I may need to share the winners' information with outside sponsors providing or shipping the prizes. The individual contest rules explain which information will be shared. If you donate to a charity (e.g., [Extra Life](http://bit.ly/TombRaiderExtraLife)) through my page, your email address is shared with that organization, and we may contact you about the following year's fundraiser.

If you [subscribe to my blog through Bloglovin'](https://www.bloglovin.com/blogs/stellas-tomb-raider-blog-7492937?widget-ref=https://blog.tombraiders.net/), you must agree to their [terms of service](https://www.bloglovin.com/tos), which include receiving promotional email from them. In order to reduce or eliminate those emails, just sign in to your Bloglovin' account and go to [Settings > Email & Notifications](https://www.bloglovin.com/settings/email).

If you have subscribed to blog updates and would like to unsubscribe, please do so through Bloglovin'. Each email from them includes a link to unsubscribe or change your email preferences.

##### LOG FILES & STATISTICS

When you visit tombraiders.net, spacecolonyfans.net, or brickraiders.net, our web server records information about your visit, including your IP (Internet Protocol) address, web browser type, operating system, as well as the referring site or search engine if applicable. This site also uses [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/) to track visitor statistics. This information is recorded in log files and used to analyze trends (e.g., which search engines and keywords were used to find this site, which pages are most popular, etc.), administer the site (e.g., find broken links), track users' movement through the site, and gather broad demographic information (e.g., users' country of origin, web browser, operating system, etc.). None of this information is linked to personally identifiable information or shared with any outside parties.

##### ADVERTISING & COOKIES

A cookie is a piece of data (in the form of a small text file) stored on a computer user's hard drive and containing information about the user. Cookies are used to personalize the information delivered to your web browser when you visit a particular web site. For example, some sites ask you to log in then use cookies to "recognize" you on subsequent visits. Some sites track your browsing preferences so they can display advertising that matches your interests, etc.

For more general information about cookies and how they work, check out this [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) entry.

My sites do not use cookies. You do not need to create a user account to access my content. However, the advertisements displayed on my pages do use cookies to track which ads a user clicks and to identify my site as the one responsible for "click-throughs" to an advertiser's site. I do not have access to or control over the cookies delivered when an ad is displayed or when a user visits an advertiser's site. Users are welcome to browse my sites with cookies disabled or to reject specific cookies if they choose. Check your web browser's help files for information on changing your privacy/cookie settings.

For specific information about the policies and practices of our ad server and affiliate programs, please visit the following sites:

Google AdSense and Affiliates - [google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)  

Please note that the products and services advertised by these companies represent numerous individual merchants. If you have questions about a specific advertiser's policies, please visit their individual sites.

For other affiliates, such as [iTunes](https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/tomb-raider/id60038777?uo=4&at=11lvvZ), [Things from Another World](http://www.shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=87029&u=49588&m=8908&urllink=&afftrack=), and [eBay](https://www.ebay.com/help/policies/member-behaviour-policies/user-privacy-notice-privacy-policy?id=4260), again please follow these links to their individual sites for more information on the data they collect.

##### LINKS

Tombraiders.net, spacecolonyfans.net, and brickraiders.net contain links to other web sites, including other fan sites as well as the game developers' sites. I try to link only to reputable sites but I am not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices of any linked sites.

##### SECURITY & DONATING TO TOMBRAIDERS.NET

Information on how to help support this site appears [here](https://tombraiders.net/stella/support/support.html). This includes links to Ko-fi.com and PayPal, through which visitors can donate money. Ko-fi partners with PayPal, which uses the highest level of encryption available. PayPal's [Security Center](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/security-main-outside) and [Privacy Policy](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/privacy-outside) provide more details. Follow this link for information about [Ko-fi.com's terms of service](https://ko-fi.com/Home/Terms). For those who prefer to donate anonymously or not to use PayPal, I also gratefully accept cash, checks, money orders, and Bitcoin. I do not publicize the donations I receive, except on [Ko-fi.com](https://ko-fi.com/stellalune) and [Extra Life](http://bit.ly/ExtraLifeStella), where donors can choose to leave their name/nickname or donate anonymously. 

Again, if you have any question about this site or its security and privacy policy, please don't hesitate to [contact me](https://tombraiders.net/stella/contact.html). —Stella
